Guide to the Sarah Hoskins photographs, 2000-2014 RL.10153
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- The Homeplace, 2000-2014; 1; 3.0 Linear Feet (250) 11x14" Silver Gelatin Prints in 5 flat boxes.
  - Prasie Ladies Day, 2003 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0103)
    Rev. Tony L. Jones and church. Keene, KY.
  - Peaches Praying, 2014 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0104)
    Peaches Hunt, who is legally blind, listening and praying at Flatwoods Church. Flatwoods, KY.
  - Derek and Trey, 2005 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0105)
    Derek Talbert and his grandson Trey praying at Maddoxtown Baptist Church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - The Keys, 2007 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0106)
    Rev. Morton holding up and handing over the keys to the deacons. His last day of pastoring in New Zion. New Zion, KY.
  - Dollars, 2009 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0107)
    Rev. Travis handing out dollar bills to the kids at Christmastime. Maddoxtown Baptist Church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - I'm Looking at You, 2008 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0108)
    Leon McDowell, one of the deacons at Maddoxtown Baptist Church, talking to the young men. He is like a big old teddy bear, kind as he can be. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - After Church, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0109)
    Derek Talbert Jr. looks at his sleeping children after church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Listening Rev. Lewis, 2010 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0110)
    Rev. Lewis listening to one of his parishioners. Jimtown, KY.
  - Fans, 2005 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0111)
    Fans in Pleasant Valley Baptisit Church on the weekend Hurricane Katrina hit New Orleans. Most of this once-black hamlet was flooded out. Boones Creek, KY.
  - Clintonville, 2013 (Box 2, Print RL10153-P-0112)
    The current Pastor was very ill and they were just trying decide if they could keep the church going. Here is Rev. Jacques Wigginton with the two current members, Ora Mae Jacobs (95 years old) and other (?). Clitonville,KY.
  - Sarah Relford, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0113)
    Sarah is waiting for the baptism to begin, which will be in her son Raymond's pool. It was supposed to be in the Elkhorn Creek, but "it was too murky." New Zion, KY.
  - Take Me To The River #1, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0114)
    Nathaniel Tanksley holding his bible waiting for the baptism to begin. New Zion, KY.
  - Walker and Water, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0115)
    Rev. Patterson getting ready to get in the pool to baptize. New Zion, KY.
  - Take Me To The River #2, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0116)
    Dr. Tamara Brown, Mitchell Gordon, and Rev. Patterson. Mitchell Gordon wanted to change his life; he decided to get baptized right before Rev. Morton was transferred. New Zion, KY.
  - Take Me To The River #3, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0117)
    Rev. Patterson prays as Mitchell Gordon dries off. New Zion, KY.
  - The Dress, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0118)
    Resting in the shelter after the baptism. New Zion, KY.
  - Back To Being A Pool, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0119)
    The baptism is over and the pool is back to being a swimming pool. New Zion, KY.
  - Shelter, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0120)
    Rev. Patterson and most of New Zion take shelter and eat down near the Elkhorn Creek after the baptism. New Zion, KY.
  - Checking The Creek, 2012 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0121)
    Rodney Talbert is already in the water as others may be looking for the snakes. New Zion, KY.
  - Creek Baptism, 2012 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0122)
    Rodney Talbert helps Rev. Patterson into the Elkhorn Creek, just a mile shy of being called a river. New Zion, KY.
  - Waiting in the Water, 2012 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0123)
    Rev. Patterson awaits the arrival of young lady to be baptized, as Rodney Talbert helps her in. New Zion, KY.
  - Kayla, 2012 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0124)
    Kayla looks up in the circle of adults as she gets ready to be baptized at Jimtown Baptist Church. Jimtown, KY.
  - Wade in the Water Kayla, 2010 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0125)
    Rev. Lewis preparing Kayla, cameras and towels are ready. Jimtown, KY.
  - Kayla and Mop, 2010 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0126)
    Kayla and her mother after she has been baptized as the wet floor is mopped. Jonestown, KY.
  - The Robe, 2010 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0127)
    Rev. Travis's baptism robe hangs to dry, Maddoxtown Baptist Church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Tijaun, 2010 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0128)
    Tijaun Neal about to be baptized by Rev. Travis as his parents look on in the refelction with the congregation of Maddoxtown Baptist Church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Empty Heart, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0129)
    My heart is empty. I loved Uncle Ernest, as I called him. His children said he would have wanted me to take pictures. Hardest thing to do. Miss him everyday. New Zion, KY.
  - Loss in New Zion, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0130)
    Ernest Talbert's son-in-law Gordon Berry at his casket. New Zion, KY.
  - Veteran Tom, 2014 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0131)
    Military honors for Tom Harbut, shelter Maddoxtown Baptist Church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Tom's Casket, 2014 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0132)
    Tom Harbut's casket being carried to the cemetery behind Maddoxtown Baptist Church. His father Will Harbut is buried there as well. They wanted Will buried next to Man O war, but the family said no. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Couples Crosses, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0133)
    These crosses are on the bed of Thomas and Allie Hocker, both 100 years old and married for 73 years. Brassfield, KY.
  - Sunday Morn, 2001 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0134)
    Otis Rankin, 93 years old. One of the very first photos I made. We laugh now as no one ever sits there. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Rev. TLJ, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0135)
    Rev. Tony Jones in his office in Keene. I was told that they would preach about evils of white people and they wouldn't be nice. Nothing could have been further from the truth. Keene,KY.
  - Rev. Cooper, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0136)
    Rev. Cooper was the former Pastor in New Zion. He came back to celebrate New Zion Days. New Zion, KY.
  - Rev. Horace Smith, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0137)
    Re. Horace Smith here in Watkinsville where he preached for over 40 years every second Sunday after he preached at Pilgrim Baptist Church, where he preached for over 60 years. The church members wanted me to photograph him with this very old desk. Watkinsville, KY.
  - Doodle's Tooth, 2009 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0138)
    Doodle Mulder's tooth at Zion Hill. Don't know his real name; everyone calls him Doodle. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Walker Boy, 2009 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0139)
    Walker Boy Beatty, one of 17 children from Frogtown. His father lost his wife and raised them all by himself. Walker Boy was one of four brothers still alive, all known by nicknames. Frogtown/Lexington, KY.
  - Myrtle B., 2011 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0140)
    Myrtle B. Hughes on her way to church. She is known by everyone for her rolls and her cooking. She has cooked for almost every farm around. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Mayor of Frogtown, 2002 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0141)
    "Hock" and Ruth Beatty on Frogtown right after church and right around Christmas. Oldest Beatty of 17 children still alive. Frogtown.
  - Miss Martha, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0142)
    Martha Rankin after church; she was one of the oldest members. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Bert and Hat, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0143)
    Bert Edwards, one of the Jimtown Male Chorus who will be singing at New Zion Days. New Zion, KY.
  - Miss Biggerstaff, 2004 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0144)
    Miss Biggerstaff standing where her house once stood in Fort Spring. She was the oldest woman church member at New Vine Baptist Church. Fort Spring, KY.
  - Milward and Memories, 2008 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0145)
    Milward "Hank" Gordon in the old cabin where his aunt, great-grandmother, and great-great-grandmother used to work on Horse Farm. Fayette County, KY.
  - Miss Margaret, 2009 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0146)
    Margaret Raglin in front of her home. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Ben, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0147)
    Ben, one of Miss Macy Simpson's grandchildren, in barn. Pricetown, KY.
  - Walter, 2005 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0148)
    Walter Edwards Horseman and memebr of Jimtown Male Chorus at Training Track. Fayette County, KY.
  - Farrier Duane, 2012 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0149)
    Duane Raglin from Zion Hill working on Three Chimneys Farm. Scott County, KY.
  - Always Horses, 2014 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0150)
    Tom "Preston" Embry back on Overbrook Farm where he used to work. He is now living there with his wife. He is still out at the training track every day except maybe Sunday. Woodford County, KY.
  - Tom, 2001 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0151)
    Tom Harbut with a copy of The Saturday Evening Post with his father Will Harbut, who was the groom of Man O War on the farm across the lane. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - The Mulders, 2009 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0152)
    Cad and Juanita Mulder sitting on their porch swing. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Rev. Hunter Byrd, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0153)
    "That white lady is here again and she got fat," Hunter Byrd on the phone. When I told one of the residents he said that, he said "that is what he says about everyone so you're good." Frogtown, KY.
  - Tribley, 2013 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0154)
    As her memory is slipping, Tribly Railey lives with her brother Charles now. They both went to the Rosenwald school at the end of the lane. Nicholasville, KY.
  - Mattie's Photos, 2006 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0155)
    Mattie C. Taylor lived in Keene. One day as we were talking she told me about the photos she took; she especially loved to photograph baptisms. Keene, KY.
  - Mother and Son, 2006 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0156)
    Garland and Agnes Jackson. I mailed him a copy of this photo like I do everyone but he called to thank me because right after I took this she had to go live in a nursing home. Russeltown, KY.
  - Mark and Jimtown Park, 2005 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0157)
    Mark Maulder in front of Jimtown Park. Jimtown, KY.
  - Kiara and Puppy, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0158)
    Kiara Johnson and puppy at New Zion Days in front of Rufas's house. New Zion, KY.
  - Baskeball Player, 2003 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0159)
    Basketball player, Uttingertown Days. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Jean, 2001 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0160)
    Jean Talbert on the front porch of her mother's home where she lives. The story of Jean is too long for here. New Zion, KY.
  - Jesse and Gun, 2009 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0161)
    Jesse Mefford and a fire with his stove or space heater. I had come by to see him and found him like this. He is amazing and made it through. Fort Spring, KY. Also known as "Slick away" or "Slip away". As slaves would escape from. I was shown a door to what was the Underground Railroad.
  - Lydia at 100, 2006 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0162)
    Lydia Talbert in her home on family reunion day. She had tuned 100 four months earlier. New Zion, KY.
  - Richard, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0163)
    Richard Hughes, first annual Zion Hill Day. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Shelby Lee Miller, 2001 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0164)
    Working on pounding out metal. Jimtown, KY.
  - Trey, 2007 (Box 3, Print RL10153-P-0165)
    Trey is standing on the stump outside of his great-great-grandmother's house. The oldest house in New Zion and in front of New Zion's historic marker. New Zion, KY.
  - Greens and Tomatoes, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0166)
    Bill Thomas's hands and greens. I never left KY without a box of vegetables from his wonderful garden in Little Georgetown. Little Georgetown, KY.
  - The Cook, 2009 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0167)
    Myrtle B. making fried chicken. She is known for all her good food. She has cooked for everyone. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Overflowing Foil Family Reunion, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0168)
    There was so much food it overflowed out of the kitchen and into the bedroom. New Zion, KY.
  - Family Prayer Reunion, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0169)
    Talbert family reunion on The Homeplace. Prayer before food. New Zion, KY.
  - Anna and Grills, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0170)
    Anna coffee and grills, Uttingertown Days. Raising money for The Lodge. Uttingertown,Ky.
  - Propane Tanks, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0171)
    Shelter behind Maddoxtown Baptist Church, fish frying and food. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Family Reunion, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0172)
    Margaret Tanksley and her granddaughter in her mother Lydia Talbert's home getting food ready for Talbert family reunion. New Zion, KY.
  - Whit, 2010 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0173)
    Whitney Hughes helping his mother set up the table for the fancy turkey shoot party. Mertle busy in the kitchen. Woodford County, KY.
  - Fixed You a Plate, 2005 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0174)
    Food being brought to the kids. Talbert reunion on The Homeplace. New Zion, KY.
  - Walker Family Reunion, 2011 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0175)
    They had the food in a little shelter where you helped yourself. Columbustown, KY.
  - Keeping Cool In Food Line, 2009 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0176)
    This was a smart woman keeping cool on one of the hot 3rd Annual Hill Days. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Plate and New Baby, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0177)
    Goodloe Family Reunion, the home of the Hocker couple married 73 years, both 100 years old. Brassfield, KY.
  - Come On In, 2011 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0178)
    Walker family reunion. Columbustown, KY.
  - The Homeplace, 2009 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0179)
    The name of this project comes from this home, The Homeplace. This is the Howard family's home in Uttingertown. The home of history and family. Every Sunday, everyone comes out to "the country". The plates and bowls are waiting. Uttingertown,KY.
  - Sunday Supper, 2014 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0180)
    Telon Gill and Tijuan Neal showing and helping elders down to Maddoxtown church basement for dinner. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Beatty Whites, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0181)
    Mrs. Caise, chief of police Anthony Beatty's mother, New Vine Cemetery Fort Spring, KY. Fort Spring, KY.
  - Boone's Creek, 2005 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0182)
    Helping up the lane and over the creek to church. Boone's Creek, Kentucky.
  - Homecoming, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0183)
    Rev. Lyle Morton and the Jimtown Male Chorus and "Fish Tail" keep cool before second service. New Zion, KY.
  - Blackbridge Homecoming, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0184)
    Girls cutting across from cemetery to church. Blackbridge, KY.
  - Otis on the Lane, 2001 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0185)
    At 93, Otis Rankin still moved fast up the lane on his way to Maddoxtown Baptist Church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Sunday Slippers, 2005 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0186)
    A young girl after Jimtown Church while the men behind her set up for Jimtown Days. Jimtown, KY.
  - Jimtown Male Chorus, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0187)
    The day I met the Jimtown Male Chorus. It was 6:00pm and they were getting ready to head into church to sing for New Zion Days. I had a 7-hour drive ahead of me and was already late. I was taking their photo and told them how I had heard all about their singing and that I felt so bad I couldn't stay and hear them. And then they sang just to me! One of the all-time special moments. New Zion, KY.
  - Ladies in White, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0188)
    Outside of New Vine Church. Fort Spring, KY.
  - Jumping Jimtown, 2004 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0189)
    Visiting children on Jimtown Days on the steps of Duncan's Chapel United Methodist Church. Jimtown is the only hamlet with two churches. Jonestown, KY.
  - New Vine, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0190)
    Deacon Ronald Taylor walking and Rev. Hunter Byrd, after church. Fort Spring, KY.
  - Hat Holding, 2005 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0191)
    Miss. Lillian Perkins holding onto her hat coming out of Uttingertown Baptist Church. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Hand Clapping, 2004 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0192)
    Girls hand-clapping after church as Pastor Travis's son Logan looks on (in black); Rev. Travis's baptismal robe dries in Maddoxtown Baptist Church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Food Line, Boone's Creek, 2005 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0193)
    Food line after church, Boone's Creek Homecoming. Boone's Creek, Kentucky.
  - UBS #128, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0194)
    Union Benevolent Society Lodge #28 Uttingertwon, KY. The lodge would give loans, help bury the dead, and provide support to each other when white America would not support them. They still do. I am now a member. They are now in their 145th at this writing. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Collecting Dues, 2008 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0195)
    Lillian Perkins writing in the amounts as her best friend Virgina Grench, and Dee Spencer on the right collect the dues. Uttingertown,KY.
  - Lodge Meeting, 2005 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0196)
    Member Anthony Stewart awaits the UBS #28 lodge meeting. Uttingertown,KY.
  - Lodge Open House, 2005 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0197)
    The lodge had been redone and they held an open house. President David (Dee) Spencer under sign with Rev. Lewis McDowell from Uttingertown Baptist Church up the lane. Uttingertown, KY.
  - David Spencer Sr. Hoeing, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0198)
    David Spencer Sr. was well up in his 80's here. He was suffering from a bit of demetia then. His old home on the left. He would come out with his wife and she would feed the chickens and he would break up the earth. They live in Lexington now, but this was his homeplace. Uttingertown, KY.
  - David Spencer Sr., 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0199)
    In front of his shed. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Princess and David Spencer, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0200)
    Princess and David Spencer at Uttingertown Days. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Putting Tools Away, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0201)
    David Spencer Sr. putting his tools away. Uttingertown, KY.
  - Father and Son, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0202)
    David "Dee" Spencer helps his father David Spencer Sr. put his jacket on after he completes his hoeing work. Uttingertown, KY.
  - The Benevolent Sisters, Their 99th Year, 2004 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0203)
    The Benevolent Sisters holding hands in prayer. They are meeting at Virgina French's home. They meet the first Thursday of every month at each other's homes. Lexington, KY.
  - The Sisters' Secrets, 2004 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0204)
    The Benevolent Sisters going over notes. L-R Virgina French, Princess Spencer, Elaine Stewart, Alberta Smith, Ophelia Jones, Anna Jackson, Cheryl McCann, Clara Jackson. Lexington, KY.
  - Collection, 2004 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0205)
    Princess Spencer collects dues for the Benevolent Sisters meeting. Lexington, KY.
  - Trouble #1, 2004 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0206)
    "Trouble #1" was what I called Virgina French as she was just plain old fun and trouble. Here she is holding up the hand, volunteering Clara Jackson for something. Princess Spencer on the right laughing. Lexington, KY.
  - Lunch is Served, 2004 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0207)
    The first Thursday of every month the sisiters meet. They take turns hosting the lunch; food is served, games often played. The minutes read and collection taken. A story too long and deep for here. Lexington, KY.
  - The Sisters After Meeting, 2011 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0208)
    The sisters walking to their cars on Upper St. Lexington, KY.
  - Georgia Sun Spot, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0209)
    Georgia Blair lived at the end of Sugarhill Lane. There were only two residents of the old hamlet living there. Here house at the now dead end road. I was warned she would shoot me. Not Georgia. She was very shy; mostly wore her white shirt and loved sweets, and my daughter as well as cats. Sugarhill, KY.
  - Georgia on her Porch, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0210)
    Georgia on her porch. Her realtives eventaully moved her out to a single apartment in some kind of a home. She misses her cats. My daughter gave her a stuffed animaal cat which she has now. Sugarhill, KY.
  - Georgia and her Cat, undated (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0211)
    Georgia and her cat. She fed all that would show up at her door, she loved them. Sugarhill, KY.
  - Georgia and Jesus, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0212)
    Georgia in her bedroom. Her pictures now hang in her living room in her apartment in Versailles. Sugarhill, KY.
  - Georgia, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0213)
    Georgia. Sugarhill, KY.
  - Derek and the Car 2011 (Box 5, Print RL10153-P-0214)
    Derek on the Lane after church and in front of his house. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Sweeping, 2009 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0215)
    Margaret Raglin sweeping in front of her home. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Mr. Winn and Lydia, 2005 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0216)
    Winston Figgs pushing Lydai Talbert into her home, Talbert family reunion. New Zion, KY.
  - Sunday Porch, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0217)
    James Jacksong and his son resting at Ft. Spring Sunday afternoon. Fort Spring, KY. Also known as "Slick away" or "Slip away". As slaves would escape from. I was shown a door to what was the Underground Railroad.
  - Change We Can Believe In, 2008 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0218)
    2nd Annual Zion Hill Days. Sleeping Boy during speeches and Obama fan. Erica Mulder? Zion Hill, KY.
  - Sisters, 2012 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0219)
    Walker sisters Clara, Katherine, and Geniva. On Katherine's front porch after church Sunday. Columbustown, KY.
  - Harbut and Triple Crown Hope, 2004 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0220)
    Tom Harbut watching Smarty Jones trying to win the Triple Crown at Blemont Park. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Truck Table, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0221)
    Andre Harris L-R-and crew. New Zion, KY.
  - Queenie is the Queen, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0222)
    One of the Relfords hits the stake in for the tent for fish fry. Queenie, Ernest Talbert's dog, thinks it is for her. New Zion, KY.
  - Goodloe Reunion, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0223)
    Goodloe Family Reunion, the home of Mr. Hocker, now 102 years old. Not sure how old the bell is. Teens and bell. Brassfield, KY.
  - Mac, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0224)
    Mac Hurt, "The best bookie and bootlegger there ever was." Not here at church but at the Bluehouse. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Derek JR, Being a Dad, 2014 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0225)
    Derek Talbert Jr. with two of his boys on the steps of Maddoxtown Baptist Church. Maddoxtown, KY.
  - Fishing and Fish Fry, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0226)
    After the pool baptism the boys managed to get out of their Sunday clothes fast. New Zion, KY.
  - Rev. Raglin, 2009 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0227)
    There are many Rev. Raglins, brothers from Zion Hill who almost all became Pastors. Here at Zion Hill Days. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Barbershop, 2003 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0228)
    Tony Lewis in back/barber working on haircuts during New Zion Days. New Zion, KY.
  - Turtle Hunting, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0229)
    Derek Talbert hunting turtles near New Zion. Scott County, KY.
  - Caught, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0230)
    Derek Talbert shows the turtle he caught, which will become soup. Scott County, KY.
  - Creek Play, 2006 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0231)
    Rev. Morton hands down a little girl to Sallie Mae Henderson's daughter. Boydtown, KY.
  - Hill Boys, 2008 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0232)
    John Devine on left and Richard Hughes on bike. Zion Hill, KY.
  - Jimown Ladies, 2004 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0233)
    Bertha Stewart, center, her daughter Treena, and Jimtown ladies getting ready for Jimtown days. Jimtown, KY.
  - Talbert Tent, 2005 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0234)
    L-R Best friends Winston Figgs and Ernest Talbert, and his son-in-law. New Zion, KY.
  - The Beasley Sisters, 2007 (Box 4, Print RL10153-P-0235)